clt20.com 2014-05-23

# Privacy Policy - CLT20.com

**PRIVACY POLICY**

This website: [www.clt20.com](http://www.clt20.com/) (“Website”) is owned and operated by Board of Control for Cricket in India (“BCCI”). Through the Website, the BCCI provides information about the Champions League Twenty20 2012 tournament, including with respect to the participating teams, fixtures and results and may allow you to comment on and post content in certain parts of the Website (“Services”).

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) reflects the BCCI’s commitment towards protecting the privacy and personal information provided by users of the Website and sets out the nature and type of information the BCCI collects from users for the purpose of the Services, the usage and disclosure of such information, and the safety and security measures adopted by the BCCI to safeguard the information.

Please note that this Policy is only applicable to the users of the Website and the information and data gathered on the Website and not to any other information or website. You are hereby advised to read this Policy carefully and fully understand the nature and purpose of gathering and/or collecting sensitive, personal and other information and the usage, disclosure and sharing of such information. By requesting and consenting to the Services, you hereby also consent to the BCCI sharing information with third party service providers engaged by the BCCI for the purpose of the Services and to the transfer and/or storage of User information and data across borders.

Terms not defined herein will have the meaning ascribed to them in the BCCI’s Terms of Use for the Website, as available at <http://www.clt20.com/about/2012/terms-and-conditions>.

This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") explains:

\--             the information we may collect about you online;

\--             the use and role of cookies and similar technologies on our Website;

\--             how we will protect and use information we collect about and from you;

\--             the circumstances in which we might disclose your details to anyone else;

\--             when we may use your details to contact you; and

\--             how you can be sure the information we hold about you is accurate and current.

**Information Gathered**

In general, you can visit our Website without revealing your identity or any personal information about yourself. However, you may not be able to access certain areas or services that require registration or need you to reveal your identity and/or other information about you.

Information that we collect from you will vary depending upon the activity you seek to engage in and may include your twitter handle, account name on social networking websites (such as Facebook), name, age, email address, place of residence and phone number. In addition, we may collect demographic information such as information about your computer, hardware, software, platform, media, Internet Protocol (IP) address and connection, information about online activity such as feature usage and click paths, and other data that you may provide in surveys or online profiles. We may combine demographic information with Personal Information to tailor our offerings or web pages to your preferences or interests.

Except for your account’s password, the BCCI does not collect any Sensitive Personal Information (“SPI”) in the course of providing the Services. SPI means such personal Information your password; physical, physiological and mental health condition; medical records and history; biometric Information, sexual orientation and financial Information (such as bank account details or credit card numbers). SPI collected by the BCCI shall not be disclosed without your express consent, save as otherwise set out in this Policy or the Terms of Use or as provided in an agreement between  the BCCI and you or as required by law. It is clarified that this condition shall not apply to publicly available information, including SPI, in relation to you on the Website.

You acknowledge that in the course of providing the Services, the BCCI may receive SPI from content posted on the Website, and hereby consent and agree to allow the BCCI to store and display the SPI collected in this manner on the Website and disclose it in the same manner as the content available on the Website.

**Personal Information**

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify you and that is not otherwise publicly available, including, but not limited to, your first and last name, age, place of residence and an email address, phone number or other contact information.

We may collect Personal Information from you when you register for any of our Services, to post comments on any forum on the Website or otherwise voluntarily provide such information. If you wish to subscribe to our marketing materials, we will use your name and email address to send the materials to you.

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

Some of our web pages may also utilise “cookies” and other tracking technologies. A “cookie” is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about your activity on our Website. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by you. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you may need to re-enter your Personal Information to gain access to certain parts of our Website.

Tracking technologies may automatically record information such as Internet domain and host names; other information about your geographic location; IP addresses; browser software and operating system types; CPU type; your manner of connecting to the Internet (e.g., connection speed through narrowband or broadband access); click paths; and dates and times that our Website is accessed.

Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Website and consequently your web experience. We may also analyse information that does not include Personal Information for trends and statistics.

**Uses of Personal Information**

We may use Personal Information and other information received and collected from you to provide the services you have requested, to enable you to access and post comments on the Website, or any part thereof, and to contact you upon your request and when otherwise necessary. We may also use Personal Information for auditing, research and analysis, and to operate and improve our services. In certain circumstances, we may share aggregated non-personal information with third parties. When we use third parties to assist us in processing your Personal Information, we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. We may also share such information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services.

Where we propose to use your Personal Information for any other uses we will ensure that we notify you first. You will also be given the opportunity to withhold or withdraw your consent for your use other than as listed above. 

**Confidentiality and Security**

We will keep confidential and protect your Personal Information except where disclosure is required or permitted by law.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and, once we receive it, for storage and disposal. All information we gather is securely stored within databases controlled by us. The databases are stored on servers secured behind a firewall; access to the servers is password-protected and is strictly limited. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We limit access to Personal Information to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

Third parties provide certain services available on our Website and on our behalf. We may provide information, including Personal Information, to third-party service providers to help us deliver our products, information, and services efficiently and effectively. Service providers are also an important means by which we maintain our Website and mailing lists. We will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third-party service providers are obligated to protect Personal Information on our behalf through confidentiality agreements and otherwise. We do not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on our behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Similarly, it is against our policy to sell Personal Information collected online without consent.

If you choose to provide us with your Personal Information, we may transfer that Personal Information from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. Your Personal Information may be collected and stored on servers located in the territory of India and such other countries as we may disclose from time to time.    

**Third Party Websites**

If you click on a link to a third party site or otherwise leave the Website, you will go to a website that is outside the purview of our control. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your Personal Information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy and security practices as we do. The use of Personal Information by such websites shall be governed by the privacy policies provided therein. Therefore, if you visit a third party website that is linked to our Website, you should consult that website's privacy policy before providing any Personal Information.

**Contacting You**

We may contact you using the Personal Information you have given us:

\--             in relation to the functioning of any service you have signed up for in order to ensure that we can deliver the services to you;

\--             where you have opted to receive further correspondence;

\--             to invite you to participate in surveys, opinion polls, etc., about the our services or otherwise (participation is always voluntary); and

\--             to provide you information about our new products and services, where you have specifically agreed to receive this.

**Change of Control**

In the event that ownership or control of the BCCI was to change, your Personal Information may be transferred. If such a transfer results in a material change in the use of your Personal Information, the BCCI will provide notice about the choices you have to decline to permit such a transfer.

**Accuracy**

To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, we wish to maintain accurate and current Personal Information. Where we collect Personal Information from you on our Website, should you need to update or correct that Personal Information, please contact us and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your Personal Information that we hold as soon as practicable. You can obtain the information we currently hold on you by emailing the BCCI at <http://www.clt20.com/about/contact>. We will use our best efforts to send you the information within 14 days of receipt of your email.

**Consent and Amendments**

By using this Website, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and to our use and management of Personal Information for the purposes and in the manner herein provided. Should this Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our Website for a reasonable period of time.

Your visit and any dispute over privacy are subject to this Privacy Policy.

**Applicable Law**

This Privacy Policy and information contained herein, shall be governed by the laws of the Republic of India and the courts of [Mumbai], India shall retain exclusive jurisdiction to entertain any proceedings in relation to any disputes arising out of the same.
